affinity.com 2014-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Affinity.com

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Affinity.com, respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Statement (the "Statement") covers the website www.affinity.com (the "Site"). We collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Site unless you choose to provide that information to us or as specifically outlined in this Statement. This Statement is incorporated into and subject to Affinity.com's Terms of Use ("TOU") found at http://affinity.com/terms.php

USE OF THIS WEB SITE CONSTITUTES ACCEPTANCE OF THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS: 

The Policy is not exhaustive and Affinity.com reserves the right to add, delete, or modify any provision of the Policy at any time without notice to yourself, effective upon the posting of the modified Policy to www.affinity.com. Please check the Site periodically for changes to the Policy. By using Affinity.com's services and/or using this Site after changes have been made to the Policy, you agree to the changes. Except when expressly agreed to the contrary in writing by an authorized representative of Affinity.com, this Policy supersedes any other agreement with Affinity.com, whether written, oral, by conduct, or otherwise. 

**Information We Collect**  
Our purpose in collecting information from you is to help us provide you with better service, such as notifications about special offers and promotions. We will not willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this Privacy Statement. Furthermore, we do not specifically target children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect, without parental consent, personally identifiable information from such children. 

If you are applying for an account with Affinity.com, we may require that you provide us with certain personal information (such as name, email address, billing information, etc.) relevant to our provision of the various services offered on the Site. We do not collect any personal information other than that which is specifically and knowingly provided to us by you. When we request information, we shall explain how it may be used and give you an opportunity to request that the information not be used for those purposes. We shall also give you an opportunity to opt out of future communications from us. 

**Cookies**  
Affinity.com may, at times, use cookies. Cookies are data files stored on your computer that identify you as a unique user. Cookies enable us to track user trends, preferences and patterns to better understand our user base and to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers permit users to refuse cookies or to be notified before a cookie is accepted. You can visit our site without using cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Affinity.com may, at times, drop third party web beacons. Opting out of third parties' services will prevent them from collecting data when a user visits any of Affinity.com's partner/customer sites. By doing so, advertisements will no longer be tailored to your interests.

To opt out of having data collected and written to cookies placed by third parties, please visit: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Note that after choosing to opt out, if you use a different computer or a different browser, or if you delete or block browser cookies, you may need to repeat the opt-out steps. Most web browsers also enable you to block browser cookies. You can refer to your web browser's documentation to get more information on how to block or delete cookies directly through your browser settings.

**Links to Other Websites**  
The Site contains links to other websites. Those websites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Affinity.com is in no way responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such third party websites. This Statement applies only to our own services and our Site, and does not apply to any other third party services or websites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit. 

**Sharing Information**  
Affinity.com may share non-personal and non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. Affinity.com may partner with other parties in connection with the various services offered on the Site. In such instances, we may share limited personal information that is necessary for the third-party to provide its services. These companies are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose. Affinity.com may also provide personal information when disclosure may be required by law (e.g., subpoenas, search warrants and court orders). We may also determine that such action is reasonably necessary to protect a party's rights, property, or well-being. This action may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud detection or protection, or in other situations involving suspicious or illegal activities. 

**Business Transfers**  
In the event of a transfer of ownership of Affinity.com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**Consent and Changes to this Privacy Statement  
**By using the Site or our services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Statement. Affinity.com may update this Statement from time to time. We may notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your information by sending a notice to you, although we are not required to do so, or we may simply place a notice on the Site. Not withstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to change this Statement without any notice whatsoever to you and for whatever reason we deem appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of the Site and our services will be construed as your acceptance of any such change. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Statement so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

Who Can I Ask If I Have Additional Questions?

Feel free to contact us at any time with any questions you may have regarding our privacy statement. 

_Effective September, 2009_
